https://www.tablelegs.com/security-and-privacy/

Table Legs
Kitchen Island Legs | 34" - 42"
Dining Table + Desk Legs | 28" - 29"
Coffee Table + Bench Legs | 14" - 18"
Side + End Table Legs | 24" - 26"
Vanity + Counter Height Table Legs | 34" - 36"
Bar Height Table Legs | 42"
Video Gallery
Information, Please!
Privacy Notice
This notice discloses the privacy policies for TableLegs.com/Classic Designs by Matthew Burak. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information collection, use, and sharing.
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only collect and have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to follow up on recent orders. You will receive additional emails regarding specials, how-tos, contests, new products or services only if you consent (opt-in) by subscribing to our email notices—which are sent every 2-3 weeks. You may unsubscribe from that list at any time using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us at info@tablelegs.com or by phone at 1-800-748-3480:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page. We do not store your credit card information.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Accounts
In order to create an account on this website, a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required. Purchasers may buy as “guests” without creating an account.
Orders
To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). Credit card data is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you. We do not store your credit card information.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Sharing
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site collects information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level or profession). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-800-748-3480 or via email at info@TableLegs.com.
Our Company
About TableLegs.com
About The Designer - Matthew Burak
Employment Opportunities
Our Quality Guarantee
Our Community
Join Our Newsletter
Read Customer Reviews
Information, Please!
Compatible Design Software and CAD Files
FAQs
×
